[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of the turtle-dove is derived from the sound it produces.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On which of these continents can you find the Salt Water Crocodile?", "correct_answer": "Australia", "incorrect_answers": ["Africa", "South America", "North America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On average, how much water is used in the USA each day?", "correct_answer": "About 340 Billion Gallons", "incorrect_answers": ["About 100 Billion Gallons", "About 200 Million Gallons", "About 900 Million Gallons"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the song Shug writes and sings for Miss Celie in the movie The Color Purple?", "correct_answer": "Miss Celies Blues", "incorrect_answers": ["Miss Celies Groove", "Miss Celies Blessings", "Miss Celies Song"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the Black dog, a ghost-like creature popular in the folklores of the British Isles?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["It is believed to appear at night.", "It is associated with the Devil.", "It is considered a portent of death."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following octopuses could most easily kill a human?", "correct_answer": "The Blue Ringed Octopus", "incorrect_answers": ["The Common Octopus", "The Giant Pacific Octopus", "Seven Armed Octopus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the creator of The Prelude, who was the Poet Laureate in England from 1843 to 1850 and comprised a group known as the Lake Poets with Samuel Taylor Coleridge and Robert Southey.", "correct_answer": "William Wordsworth", "incorrect_answers": ["John Donne", "Lord Byron", "Robert Browning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Made in 1952 in black and white, this movie is the highest ranked western film (# 33) among the AFI Top 100 American movies.", "correct_answer": "High Noon", "incorrect_answers": ["The Magnificent Seven", "Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid", "The Searchers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do the villains from the War of the Worlds, ranked #27 on the AFIs list of the 50 top villains, have in common with the villain at #14 from the same list?", "correct_answer": "They both come from outer space.", "incorrect_answers": ["They both are Nazis,", "They both are gang leaders,", "They both are women,"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Dead Sea, the lowest point on Earth, is how far below sea level?", "correct_answer": "418 meters", "incorrect_answers": ["349  meters", "517  meters", "2608 meters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During the sermon on the mount in the movie Monty Pythons Life of Brian, the characters mistake one of the beatitudes. According to them blessed are which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Cheesemakers", "incorrect_answers": ["Eunuchs", "Cow milkers", "Romans"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is a day longer than a year?", "correct_answer": "On Mercury", "incorrect_answers": ["At the North and South Poles", "On Mars", "On Pluto"]}]